So friends, you all know that ICC Bank is a
very big bank. Today's profile has
come from ICC Bank for the
post of insurance agent.
Now you all know that many sir banks are selling
insurance, so ICC Bank has
also prepared for selling insurance on Monday,
so both male and female can apply for the post of insurance agent.
Talking about educational qualification,
10th pass is eligible
and
talking about further criteria, then minimum age should be 18
years.
No paper and you will not have to do any paper.
Everyone can work
in this, you
can work from your mobile sitting at home and by doing
part time, now there is a very good
special honorable job in this,
if you do it, then by selling insurance to all the
sirs, your friends, relatives and family
members in your office, you
can generate a good commission every month. By doing that
part time, by reducing your part
time a little bit, if you take out
one or two hours daily in this part time job, then
I said that somehow you will get
50-60 thousand commission,
so in this job and  What benefits will you get,
how to apply,
I will tell you everything in detail in the next video, I will
show you everything in detail on my mobile screen,
before that if you are new to the channel then
subscribe to the channel and definitely press the bell icon
and if you liked today's video then definitely give a
like and comment how you liked the video, so
let's start the video, keep watching the video
on your mobile screen without skipping,
now you are
watching the video on my mobile screen, then
you can see that the
website of ICC Bank has been opened,
I have already given the link in the description of the video,
from there you can go directly to this page,
here you
can see the general insurance agent below, I Partner Pro BN
Insurance Patna
Zero Investment Business, you will
not have to invest even a single rupee,
everything will be done directly online
[Music]
Being one of the leading players in the
market, they provide this
platform to sell insurance, it's simple,
conveyance and recording
along with commission, you will get it according to the amount you earn.  It is
telling you that you will also be given a salary from it.
Now you can see below that working directly with
ICC Lombot
means you will work directly in ICC Bank, there will be no
agency or consultancy in between, work
part time. There is no fixed time in this, you have to take out
time as per your convenience and work.
Policy insurance will be instant, there will be no
change,
no paperwork is needed to close sales. You do
not have to do any paperwork to get insurance done.
Teamly commission payout. Every insurance has its
own commission and
you will be given a team commission.
Easy digital claims. Whatever
insurance you get will have a digital claim in it.
Insurance will also be digital and the claim will
also be digital in it. There is no paperwork. There are
many types of insurance here. Live
insurance, tax insurance, business
insurance, there are many types of insurance. You will
get different commissions for different insurances. You can see below.
You can see some details in its bigger form
now. Type, policy, sample
premium, applicable commission rates, commission. And
if you get a tax insurance done, if
for example the premium of insurance is Rs. 25000,
then you will get 15% commission.
If you get car insurance of ₹25000
done from any person then you will
get commission directly of 3750.
After that see insurance, if you
get bike insurance of ₹1500 then you will get
15% commission in that. You will
also get 10% commission in business insurance
and there are details too, I will tell you later.
After that you can see Mr.
Billing Mrs. Business day after tomorrow. Sir, some
details have been given in this, now read it out
once. What's the process of
Agent through iPartner,
see download and create an account. I have
given the link of the application in the description of the video, you
can download from there. Otherwise you can also
download the application by typing iPartner Pro from Google Play.
After that
see below, verify your document, education will be
credited in the account. You
can see tech and 15 more training and
give the POCP exam. You can do this from the
comfort of your home.
Your ICC Bank
training will be given after giving the training. There
is IRDA, is there a small exam in
it?  You just have to pass, it is very
simple,
you will first be given training on how to
clear the exam, after that you have to
clear the exam, after that you will
become a direct insurance agent, you
can work from your mobile, you do
n't even have to write any paper, there is no need to know the story,
now you can see below, more details have been given,
you can read out in it, it is
written in it, see what exactly is it,
P what RD benefit of partnering
ICC Lombard POCP and iPartner
Pro, you can read out everything in it, what
is the eligibility, what document do
you need,
see in it, photo is required, PAN card is required, address
proof, address proof is your driving
license, passport or light bill, any one will be valid,
10th and 12th class marksheet,
any marksheet of 10th or 12th class will be accepted
in it and photo upload from cancelled cheque and NEFT,
now if it is of bank account then you
can upload its photo as well or you
can also upload the photo of cancelled cheque,
you need to complete
your work while doing it or if college  I am a
student, even while studying you can reduce your
daily work by half an hour, one hour or two hours and by doing
part time you
can generate good income. How did you like the video,
please do tell me by commenting in the comment box and if you liked the
video then give it a like and if you have
created a channel then subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon, thank you.